fear what is it how are they formed can
恐惧是什么？它们是如何形成的？
we get rid of our fears and what is
我们能否摆脱恐惧？
going on in the brain while all this
当这一切发生时，大脑中正在发生什么？
happens first let's define fear fear is
首先让我们定义恐惧。恐惧是
a primitive emotion resulting in a set
一种原始情绪，会导致由
perceived imminent threat some of these
感知到的迫在眉睫的威胁引发的一系列功能变化。 这些
functional changes include rapid heart
功能变化包括心率加快、
rate shortness of breath nausea tensing
呼吸急促、恶心、
of muscles and pupil dilation which have
肌肉紧张和瞳孔扩张，这些都是
all been eled in the fight or flight
在战斗或逃跑
response preparing our body to fight or
反应中引起的，从进化的角度来看，恐惧的主要目的是让我们的身体做好战斗或
flee a fearful stimulus from an
逃离可怕刺激的准备。
purpose of fear is to promote survival
促进生存
those that feared the right threat
那些害怕正确威胁的人
survived reproduced and passed Their
得以生存下来，并将他们的
Fear to their offspring those that
恐惧传递给他们的后代 那些
didn't fear the right threats well I
不太害怕正确威胁的人 我
think you know what happened so the
想你知道发生了什么，所以
question remains what is going on in the
问题仍然是大脑中发生了什么
brain to trigger these fear responses
触发这些恐惧反应
our answer lies with the amydala found
答案在于
in the middle of the brain towards the
位于大脑中部、
top of the temporal lobe the amydala is
颞叶顶部的杏仁核。杏仁核是
the brain's main Center for emotion
大脑情绪
regulation and is specifically
调节的主要中心，在结构上与
associated with processing fearful
处理恐惧刺激特别相关。杏仁核
up of several groups of nuclei some of
由几组核组成，其中一些是
which are included in this diagram in
在
the presence of a fearful stimulus
存在可怕的刺激时，
sensory areas of the brain provide
大脑的感觉区域会
information to the input area of the
向杏仁核的输入区域提供信息，处理后杏仁核的
amydala once process the output areas of
输出区域会向下
hypothalamus triggering the release of
丘脑发送信号，触发皮质醇的释放，这是
cortisol our body's main stress hormone
我们身体的主要应激激素
and the activation of the autonomic
自主神经系统的激活（
system that regulates things like heart
调节
rate digestion and respiration both
心率、消化和呼吸等身体无意识系统）既让
prepare our bodies to fight or flight
我们的身体做好战斗或逃跑的准备，
and are responsible for the production
又负责产生
of fear respons is so far we've
恐惧反应，到目前为止，我们已经
explained why someone may fear a
解释了为什么有人可能会害怕 对
stimulus that poses a threat to survival
生存构成威胁的刺激
however this does not explain why
但这并不能解释为什么
someone may have a fear of something
有人可能会害怕一些
unthreatening let's say ducks but
不具威胁性的东西，比如说鸭子，但
classical conditioning may have the
经典条件反射可能
answer in the context of fear classical
在恐惧的背景下有答案经典条件
conditioning is mainly conducted on rats
反射主要在老鼠身上进行，
a typical experiment will involve an
典型的实验将涉及
unconditioned stimulus a painful shock
无条件反射 刺激
that produces an unconditioned response
产生无条件反应的痛苦电击
a fear response a neutral stimulus a
恐惧反应 中性刺激
tone is also presented producing no
也出现音调 产生无
response when a painful shock is paired
反应 当疼痛电击
with a tone a fearful response is
与音调配对时
produced over time the repetition of
随着时间的推移产生恐惧反应 重复
this pairing will result in the rack
这种配对将导致机架
producing a fearful response to the now
产生 对当前
condition tone alone resulting in a
条件音的恐惧反应会导致
condition response however can this be
条件反应，但这是否可以
applied to humans let's find out using
应用于人类呢？让我们找出使用
our unsuspecting subject replacing the
我们毫无戒心的受试者，用
shock with being shot and the tone with
被射击代替震惊，用嘎嘎声代替音调
quacking to classically condition the
来经典地调节对
fear of ducks first we will present the
鸭子的恐惧，我们首先将介绍
alone next we will present the subject
接下来，我们将向受试者单独提供
with the neutral stimulus
中性刺激，
alone excellent our subject is
非常好，我们的受试者正在以我们
neutral stimuli in a way we would expect
期望的方式对无条件刺激和中性刺激做出反应，
now we will repeatedly pair these
现在我们将反复将这些刺激配对
together let's see if we have
在一起，让我们看看我们是否具有
classically conditioned the fear of duct
经典的条件刺激
by presenting our subject with a now
通过向我们的受试者提供当前
condition stimulus to observe if a fear
条件刺激来观察是否
response was
形成恐惧反应，
formed it would appear we've managed
看起来我们已经将
condition fear of duct into our subject
管道恐惧控制到我们的受试者中，
but what is going on in the brain to
但是大脑中发生了什么形成了
form this condition fear let's go back
这种条件恐惧让我们走吧
to the amydala to find out in the
回到杏仁核，发现在
presence of the uncondition stimulus
存在无条件刺激的情况下，
signals from sensory areas of the brain
来自大脑感觉区域的信号
are strong enough to activate the
足够强大，可以激活
amydala and trigger a fear response in
杏仁核并引发恐惧反应；在
the presence of a neutral stimulus the
存在中性刺激的情况下，来自
signals from sensory areas of the brain
大脑感觉区域的信号则
are not strong enough to activate the
不会
Amala therefore produce no fear response
因此，
when the unconditioned a neutral stimuli
当无条件的中性刺激
are repeatedly paired a fear response is
重复配对时，不会产生恐惧反应，
produced as synaptic connections between
因为
sensory areas in the amydala become
杏仁核中感觉区域之间的突触连接变得
stronger making it easier to send a
更强，从而更容易发送导致
signal that results in a fear response
恐惧反应的信号，从而产生恐惧反应
now when the newly conditioned stimulus
当新的条件刺激
is presented the sinapic connections are
出现时，sinapic连接是
so strong and sensitive the signal
如此强大和敏感，
produced is able to activate the amydala
产生的信号能够单独激活杏仁核，
alone producing a fear response so if we
产生恐惧反应，所以如果我们
can condition a fear does this mean we
能够调节恐惧，这是否意味着我们
can get rid of it many clinical
可以摆脱它许多针对
therapies for phobias are based on
恐惧症的临床疗法 基于
classical conditioning one of the most
经典条件反射，其中最
prominent being flooding this involves
突出的一种是洪水，这涉及
the patient confronting their fears
患者面对他们的恐惧，
aiming to break the bond between the
旨在打破
condition stimulus and response as over
条件刺激和反应之间的联系，随着
time the patient realizes that the
时间的推移，患者意识到
fearful stimulus does not pose a threat
恐惧的刺激不会构成威胁
and begins to
并开始
relax
放松